# **Eugene Lay Chai Chun**

Singapore, Singapore / eugenelcc@hotmail.com / +65 96604238

# **Summary**

Hello! I'm Eugene Lay

Self-driven to learn something new to further enhance my understanding. I used to be a normal academic student

I am now a Graduate student of Diploma Information technology at Nanyang Polytechnic (NYP). Specialized in different type of Programming languages, Python, C# and JavaScript to enforce my learning experience.

My Year 3 Specialization in Nanyang Polytechnic, I was taught and learned the basic of an Artificial Intelligence (AI) & Machine learning(ML) fundamental. Would continue to explore more software's and new programming languages in the IT Field.

#### LinkedIn

#### Education

# **Diploma of Information Technology**

Nanyang Polytechnic , Singapore, Singapore 03/2022

- Singapore Edusave Good Progress Award (2021)
- · Nanyang Polytechnic Diploma of Information Technology certificates (2022)

# Singapore-Cambridge O'Level

Peirce Secondary School, Singapore, Singapore 09/2018

- Singapore Edusave Good Progress Award (2014)
- National Youth Achievement Award Singapore (2016)
- Singapore-Cambridge Normal(Academic) Level (2017)
- · Singapore-Cambridge Ordinary Level (2018)

# **Primary School Leaving Exam (PSLE)**

Kheng Cheng School, Singapore, Singapore 09/2013

- Edusave Good Progress Award (2011)
- CDC & CCC Good Progress Award (2010)
- Kheng Cheng Best in progress (2013)
- Primary School Leaving Exam (PSLE) (2013)

#### **Experience**

#### **IHiS (Integrated Health Information Systems)**

Information Technology Service Assistant , Singapore, Singapore 03/2022 - 04/2022

- Identified and resolved issues using software and hardware.
- Extending my contract with my previous Internship company to continue improving my skills and knowledge under them

## **IHiS (Integrated Health Information Systems)**

Project Analyst Internship, Singapore, Singapore 09/2021 - 02/2022

- Experience the role of project analyst in combining both healthcare and information technology together to create a solution and mitigate problem. Experiencing working in a Healthcare-IT sector
- Developed documentation and reports to showcase storyboarding and improve decision-making.
- Conducted pre- and post-action analysis of operational decision-making to review impact.
- · Conducting research and IT service available to integrate use cases problem

### **Ipsos**

Field Work, Singapore, Singapore 03/2019 - 03/2019

- Conduct a 1 on 1 interviews with parents and survery them for testing of Milk powder project for their child to taste
- Milk Powder Project, having to survey 30 different parents to test a prototype milk powders for their child -
- Crowd Control and friendly interactions with both the parents and child -
- Having to set up milk powders and serve it to the parents

#### **Skills**

Project Management, Documentation review, UI/UX, Python , Decision making, Communication skills, Physical fitness, Running

#### **Awards**

CDC & CCC Good Progress Award (2010), Edusave Good Progress Award (2011), Kheng Cheng Best in progress (2013), Edusave Good Progress Award (2014), Ngee Ann Polytechnic achievement in Youth Entrepreneurship, National Youth Achievement Award – Bronze (2016)